cookingnook.com 2016-11-08

# Privacy statement for Cookingnook.com | Cookingnook.com

| February 25, 2013

We recognize the importance of protecting the privacy of information collected about our customers and prospective customers as well as disclosing to users of this site any affiliations we have that benefit us financially.

This privacy statement has been created in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy and openness.

The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this web site.

Any information provided by users of this site or emailed to this office is collected for the purpose of better serving the user’s needs and is **not** passed on in any way to any other person, organization or website.

**That is our promise to you.**

## Terms of Use

This site contains informational material and is not intended to give health or other professional advice. Please consult your personal physician before making any significant changes in your diet and lifestyle. By using this web site, you agree to be bound by the terms and conditions and privacy policy.

## Links, Ads and Affiliation Disclosure

This site is my personal site. It accepts advertising and other forms of compensation. Such compensation does NOT influence the information contained on this site. We always give our honest opinions, findings, beliefs, or experiences as we really do believe that honesty is the best policy for all.

We work hard to ensure that the information contained on our web pages is accurate, relevant and of the high quality that our visitors have come to expect.

This site contains links to other sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of such Web sites. We are not responsible for any content on any linked sites or for any goods or services available from them.

We use ads from Google on this website. This is what you need to know about Google:

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site.
  * Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to users based on their visit to this site and/or other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

“Ads by Google” are not selected by me, so if you see a Google ad and a Web page about the same product or service, it is a coincidence.

I only accept non-Google sponsorships from providers of high-quality goods or services. I appreciate their recognition and support of this site.

I sometimes recommend products or services on the pages of this site. Although I have not purchased and tried every product or service I recommend, I do only recommend products from those sites that I consider to be quality websites. That said, you should know that if you purchase a product recommended on this site, I probably make a small commission on that purchase. It helps keep this site going and is a standard practice on most websites you will visit.

But do believe me – promoting junk would not only hurt you, it would hurt me too, as it would eventually bring down the reputation of this site I have taken so much time to lovingly build over the years. I have no intention of doing that and I respect my visitors. So the recommendations I make are for goods and services that I honestly believe are of value.

I appreciate your support of my sponsors and recommendations. This site takes time and effort to deliver original content, free, to you. Supporting my sponsors is a WIN-WIN-WIN for you, me, and them. Thank you very much.

## Security

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control.

## Changes to this Policy

CookingNook.com reserves the right to change this policy at any time. Please check this page periodically for changes. Your continued use of our site following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes.

This policy and the use of this Site are governed by Ontario law. If a dispute arises under this Policy we agree to first try to resolve it with the help of a mutually agreed-upon mediator in the following location: Toronto, Ontario, Canada.

CookingNook.com is controlled, operated and administered entirely within St. Catharines, Ontario. This statement and the policies outlined herein are not intended to and do not create any contractual or other legal rights in or on behalf of any party.

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, terms of use or your dealings with this Web site, you may contact:

Karen Ciancio  
Click here to email me.
